<contentList>
    <content contentuid="h278b2bccg1afcg4314gbfcbgb10105ebc12b" comment="Morning Person description">When resurrected, you resurrect to full health. You begin combat with maximum AP.</content>
    <content contentuid="h42b4c1e3g7c07g400dg8924g2807a024e6bb" comment="Pet Pal description">Pet Pal enables you to talk to animals. Also increases your maximum number of summons by 1, but reduces their damage and Vitality by 50%.</content>
    <content contentuid="h6a4d6da0g29cfg44ecg8913g5a0a76cf1bbd" comment="Arrow Recovery description">Arrow Recovery provides a 33% chance to recover a special arrow after shooting it. Also removes the close-quarter damage penalty of ranged weapons.</content>
    <content contentuid="h18f97d5bg9a79g4917g809dgb0ac7a5ec302" comment="Strength description">Increases all damage by 3% per point. Physical damage is further increased by 3% per point, and damaging statuses by 5% per point. Allows you to lift and carry heavier items.</content>
    <content contentuid="h6b67efcagf943g43a1g959eg36f9ecc42e7e" comment="Intelligence description">Increases all damage by 3% per point. Damage dealt by skills is further increased by 3% per point, and Accuracy is increased by 2% per point.</content>
    <content contentuid="h6d76eb15gdb1ag4ebeg8001g58173516a923" comment="Walk It Off description">Walk It Off reduces all status durations by 1 turn, including positive statuses. Does not affect statuses with a duration of 1 turn. Also increases all resistances by 10% each time you are hit by a character, up to a maximum of 50%, until the next turn.</content>
    <content contentuid="h75391bafg8744g4441g9b1egf52f182f96fc" comment="Finesse description">Increases all damage by 3% per point. Gain 1% Dodge per point and increase movement by 0.15m per AP per point.</content>
    <content contentuid="h81ca938fg5ef4g452agb093g1294e2f0718b" comment="Leech description">Leech heals you when standing in blood. Also increases Lifesteal by 25%.</content>
    <content contentuid="h878c02c0gc629g470dg955cg80dc2a125cb2" comment="Stench description">Stench decreases everyone&apos;s attitude towards you by [2], but melee opponents find you less attractive in combat. Also increases your Poison resistance by 30% and makes you immune to Diseased.</content>
    <content contentuid="h8ddc8dd4ge8feg4420ga6dag0d87ce8ec743" comment="Duck Duck Goose description">[1] lets you evade attacks of opportunity. Also increase your Dodge by 5% and Movement by 1m per AP.</content>
    <content contentuid="hbde985cfgb1c4g4bb6g9a61gbec72c9b4ed6" comment="Mnemonic description">Mnenomic doubles all points invested in Memory.</content>
    <content contentuid="hc453e399ge1f5g41f1gaeabgcdd4de833c63" comment="Demon or IceKing">A character with [1] has an extra 30% [3], but takes a [4]% penalty to [5]. Additionally, the maximum [3] is raised by [6]. Demon grants 20% additional damage on all Burning and Necrofire statuses you apply to enemies. Ice King increases all Water damage you deal by 20%.</content>
    <content contentuid="hcb8f9837gdf0fg4a01ga7d6g5ed522b74189" comment="Escapist description">[1] allows you to flee combat even when enemies are close by. Also makes you immune to Crippled, Entangled and Enwebbbed.</content>
    <content contentuid="he94327f7g293dg488eg9d25gcb4f7ae7be24" comment="HotHead description">While above 75% Vitality, Hothead provides 10% Critical Chance and 10% Chance to Hit. Chance to Hit is a flat bonus unaffected by Accuracy and Dodge.</content>
    <content contentuid="hf3cd8067g36c0g4b48ga4dfg361f33579b43" comment="Ambidextrous description">Ambidextrous reduces the cost of using grandes and scrolls by 1 AP when your off-hand is free. Also provides 2 free equipment switches per turn.</content>
    <content contentuid="hf4632a8fg42a7g4d53gbe26gd203f28e3d5e" comment="Shadow damages ?">Shadow</content>
    <content contentuid="hfb8eec35g3339g4762g8382g712e74a2ac0b" comment="Slingshot description">[1] adds an extra [2]m range to your grenade throws and increase their damage by 30%.</content>
    <content contentuid="hfc8981a1g8f84g49c8ga8b4g17564a836c45" comment="Duelist description">Duelist increases AP Start and Recovery by 1 and Maximum by 2 if you are wielding a Single-Handed weapon with a free off-hand.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd980a2a1gc33eg4810gafc8g07f55ba70245" comment="Duelist displayname">Duelist</content>
    <content contentuid="h768669d0g02adg48f7g901eg83068a96bf19" comment="Dual-Wielding description">Dual-Wielding increases damage and Dodging when wielding two Single-Handed weapons. Also increases off-hand damage by 10% per point.</content>
    <content contentuid="h03d68693g35e7g4721ga1b3g9f9882f08b12" comment="Dual-Wielding displayname">Dual-Wielding</content>
    <content contentuid="h54f2ea13g97dbg4b86g9d13geeb81186faca" comment="Ranged description">[1] increases damage and Critical Chance when using bows and crossbows. Also increases the range by 0.5m per point when wielding a bow, crossbow or wand(s).</content>
    <content contentuid="h751cb9fcgcc15g485fg80dag96d013bb5fff" comment="Single-handed description">Single-Handed increases damage and Accuracy when using a single-handed weapon (dagger, sword, axe, mace or wand) with a shield or empty off-hand. Also increases armors by 6% and resistances by 2% per point.</content>
    <content contentuid="h206ce4abg4f84g4b2dg934aga0d96a602f2c" comment="Two-handed descripiton">Two-Handed increases damage and Critical Multiplier when using two-handed melee weapons (swords, axe, mace, spear or staff). Also grants 2% Chance to Hit per point. Chance to Hit is a flat bonus unaffected by Accuracy and Dodge.</content>
    <content contentuid="hf3893f8fg20c5g4078ga83cgef8783082103" comment="All Skilled up description">The first skill used during your turn has its cooldown reduced by 1 turn.</content>
    <content contentuid="h90812fdfg4f53g49afg8a97g42aefdeb508c" comment="Savage Sortilege description">Savage Sortilege allows all magical skills to Critically Strike. Also increases your Critical Chance by 10% (applied multiplicatively after all other bonuses).</content>
    <content contentuid="h1bae56a9ga45fg431fg80bfg2afbef03c1d2" comment="Perseverance description">Perseverance restores Magic Armour on recovering from Frozen or Stunned, and restores Physical Armour on recovering from Knocked Down or Petrified. Additionally, 2% of maximum Vitality is restored per point.</content>
    <content contentuid="h9df517d1gf64bg499dgb23fg462fd1f061bc" comment="Critical chance description">Your chance to Critically Strike when attacking with a weapon or when using a skill that is weapon-based. If you Backstab, your Critical Chance is converted to additional damage in a ratio of 1% Critical Chance to 2% damage.</content>
    <content contentuid="hb924258ag2cf7g4c11gaf4eg8b7de303c197" comment="Attributes dynamic bonus"> </content>
    <content contentuid="h278d3a4fg4dceg4362g9b35g9c3685c93268" comment="Damage tooltip">The damage you inflict when successfully hitting an enemy or object. This number does not account for attribute bonuses.</content>
    <content contentuid="h8256bf13gb4cag4662gaafegb5724b210c92" comment="Leadership description">[1] grants Dodging and Resistance bonuses to all allies in a 16m radius.</content>
</contentList>
