<contentList>
	<content contentuid="h278b2bccg1afcg4314gbfcbgb10105ebc12b" comment="Morning Person description">When resurrected, you resurrect to full health. You also start the combats with all your AP.</content>
	<content contentuid="h42b4c1e3g7c07g400dg8924g2807a024e6bb" comment="Pet Pal description">[1] enables you to talk to animals. Also increases your max number of summons by 1 but reduce their damages and Vitality by 50%.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6a4d6da0g29cfg44ecg8913g5a0a76cf1bbd" comment="Arrow Recovery description">[1] gives you [2]% chance to recover a special arrow after shooting it. You are also not penalized by the close-quarter damage penalty on ranged weapons anymore.</content>
	<content contentuid="h18f97d5bg9a79g4917g809dgb0ac7a5ec302" comment="Strength description">Strength increases all your damages by 3% per point, 3% more for all weapon-based attack, statuses will do 5% more damage per point and allows you to lift and carry heavier items.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6b67efcagf943g43a1g959eg36f9ecc42e7e" comment="Intelligence description">Intelligence increases all your damages by 3% per point, increases damages from skills by 3% per point and your Accuracy by 2% per point.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6d76eb15gdb1ag4ebeg8001g58173516a923" comment="Walk It Off description">[1] reduces all status durations by 1 turn, including positive statuses. Does not affect statuses with a duration of 1 turn. Also increase all your resistances by 10% each time you take a hit from a character, up to 50% until the next turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h75391bafg8744g4441g9b1egf52f182f96fc" comment="Finesse description">Finesse increases all your damages by 3% per point, you gain 1% dodge and 0.15 Movement per point.</content>
	<content contentuid="h81ca938fg5ef4g452agb093g1294e2f0718b" comment="Leech description">[1] heals you when standing in blood. Also increase your Lifesteal by 25%.</content>
	<content contentuid="h878c02c0gc629g470dg955cg80dc2a125cb2" comment="Stench description">[1] decreases everyone&apos;s attitude towards you by [2], but melee opponents find you less attractive in combat. Also increases your Poison resistance by 30% and make you immune to Diseased.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8ddc8dd4ge8feg4420ga6dag0d87ce8ec743" comment="Duck Duck Goose description">[1] lets you evade attacks of opportunity. Also increase your Dodge by 5% and Movement by 1.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbde985cfgb1c4g4bb6g9a61gbec72c9b4ed6" comment="Mnemonic description">[1] double the points you invested in Memory.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc453e399ge1f5g41f1gaeabgcdd4de833c63" comment="Demon or IceKing">A character with [1] has an extra 30% [3], but takes a [4]% penalty to [5]. Additionally, the maximum [3] is raised by [6]. Demon grants 20% additional damage on Burning and Necrofire you deal. Ice King increases Water damages you deal by 20%.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcb8f9837gdf0fg4a01ga7d6g5ed522b74189" comment="Escapist description">[1] allows you to flee combat even when enemies are right next to you. Also makes you immune to Crippled, Entangled and Web.</content>
	<content contentuid="he94327f7g293dg488eg9d25gcb4f7ae7be24" comment="HotHead description">While you are at 75% or more Vitality, [1] grants you an extra [2]% critical chance and [3]% more Chance to hit! Chance to hit is better than Accuracy since it provide a flat bonus.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf3cd8067g36c0g4b48ga4dfg361f33579b43" comment="Ambidextrous description">[1] reduces the cost of using grenades and scrolls by [2] AP when your offhand is free. Also provide 2 free equipment switch per turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf4632a8fg42a7g4d53gbe26gd203f28e3d5e" comment="Shadow damages ?">Shadow</content>
	<content contentuid="hfb8eec35g3339g4762g8382g712e74a2ac0b" comment="Slingshot description">[1] adds an extra [2]m range to your grenade throws. Also increase their damages by 30%</content>
	<content contentuid="hfc8981a1g8f84g49c8ga8b4g17564a836c45" comment="Bigger and better description">[1] increases AP Start, recovery by 1 and max by 2 if the character have a one handed weapon with the offhand free.</content>
	<content contentuid="h768669d0g02adg48f7g901eg83068a96bf19" comment="Dual Wielding description">[1] increases damage and Dodging when dual-wielding two one-handed weapons. Also increase offhand damage by 10% per point.</content>
	<content contentuid="h54f2ea13g97dbg4b86g9d13geeb81186faca" comment="Ranged description">[1] increases damage and Critical Chance when using bows and crossbows. Also increase the range by 0.5m per point when wielding bow, crossbow or wand (also when dual-wielding).</content>
	<content contentuid="h751cb9fcgcc15g485fg80dag96d013bb5fff" comment="Single-handed description">[1] increases damage and Accuracy when using a single-handed weapon (dagger, sword, axe, mace or wand) with a shield or empty off-hand. Also increase armors by 6% and resistances by 2% per point.</content>
	<content contentuid="h206ce4abg4f84g4b2dg934aga0d96a602f2c" comment="Two-handed descripiton">[1] increases damage and the Critical Multiplier when using two-handed melee weapons (sword, axe, mace, spear or staff). Also grants 2% of Chance to Hit per point. Chance to Hit provide a flat bonus to hit and thus is better than Accuracy.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf3893f8fg20c5g4078ga83cgef8783082103" comment="All Skilled up description">The first skill used during your turn have its cooldown reduced by 1 turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h90812fdfg4f53g49afg8a97g42aefdeb508c" comment="Savage Sortilege description">[1] gives all magical skills a critical chance equal to your critical chance score. Also multiply your Critical Chance by 110%.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1bae56a9ga45fg431fg80bfg2afbef03c1d2" comment="Perseverance description">[1] restores Magic Armour after you recover from [2] or [3], and restores Physical Armour after [4] or [5]. You also regain 2% of your maximum Vitality per point.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9df517d1gf64bg499dgb23fg462fd1f061bc" comment="Critical chance description">How much chance you have to strike a critical attack when attacking with a weapon or when using a skill that is weapon-based. If you backstab, each percent in Critical Chance provide you a bonus of 2% damage.</content>
</contentList>